from Ms. Pierson for me
to be chalk monitor that year.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
I needed to hear that.
(Penny:)Why can't Leonard understand it?
(Sheldon:)Because he's not like us, Penny.
(Sheldon:)We're dreamers.
(Penny:)Yeah, I need to start cracking the
window when I leave you in the car.
(Sheldon:)Hey.
(Amy:)Hello, Bert.
(Bert:)So, anyway, there's this big
rock and mineral show
next week in Santa Monica and--
Listen... Bert, before you
say anything else, I...
(Amy:)I have a boyfriend.
(Bert:)Oh. This is awkward.
(Bert:)You thought I was gonna ask you
to go with me to the mineral show.
(Amy:)Weren't you?
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Amy:)That's very nice of you,
but I do have a boyfriend.
(Bert:)That's what you all say.